sup guys
Oh pilot zero point three point nine
I'm rollin with the new model
so yeah
it's pretty good it's cutting a little
on left I'm gonna review this stuff in
the replay the silky-smooth feels
amazing check it out when you're coming
to a stop behind like like a car at a
stoplight or something it's so much more
smooth than it used to be in the Sun a
Honda Civic there's also minor bug fix
it feels really good
dropping an employee off at the airport
like holidays or something
it's being presenting
hey Kirk 3d
take control oh yeah just cuz the term
is sharp and hit the torque limit it's
alright
what's up today nothing much so yeah the
so compiled at zero point nine zero
point three point nine it's actually all
the way already out in the development
branch so you guys can download and
enjoy we've also shipped support for the
Toyota Prius so Prius support can be
yours if you download zero see what it's
gonna do here
nice
which Jen creates so all the Priuses
with TS SP
it doesn't like a priest to priest a
priest for that doesn't matter we have
the latest gen but it work on the
previous gen as well I think actually
all the message isn't the same all right
coming in hot
and to control was to break get my foot
on the brake that's my age but you can
also engage now with your foot on the
gas but you can't if you press the gas
it will disengage so if I press the gas
here let's see if we can get one of
those silky smooth with MVC stops right
up here I'll feel this guy's this is
this is silky smooth that's better than
Tesla and they have regen too oh that
that's like sometimes you would want to
like disengage and you do a hard stop
was coming not not with this
so how come my comma hoodie you can buy
these at chop comma dot III by OD by so
yeah we can go through yeah the test the
breaking definitely sucks on AP one we
can go through let's go through what we
have here
so this isn't yawn hoodies aren't
comfortable right this is a giraffe
this is a pandal and this is us going
to do here and help out the steering
so that was about the only tour coming
anyway which car performs the best
probably a Honda Civic still we want it
to be the Prius the Prius has a few
annoying things about it we'll see if we
can fix them no we're never going to
support phones other than the one plus
three this here is a Honda Civic and
it'll be na Jersey no no no no only the
one plus three and three teen is all
that will be supported
Civic doesn't have phasers not only
cruises have phasers man we found the
phasers arms could be great only with an
open pilot gold subscription gold masks
like 4chan gold you know no one no one
should let me run a company man
e Honda cr-v the only of the 2015-16 one
and we support all a Toyota rav4 which
is the third most popular car in the
world right now so yeah they're good to
have look at this look at this silky
smooth break behind this FedEx truck
silky smooth oh that feels good no no
Subarus man I don't know what any
Subarus I don't actually know anyone in
your life well it's a Subaru I'm
convinced that the whole Subaru channel
is just Subaru employees doesn't work on
curvy back roads the Civic has a very
restrictive torque limit so not really
the rf4 works pretty well yeah by all
means port to a Mercedes Class A I don't
know what country you're from we don't
have class ace here we have C Z's and SS
yes
what about inclines seems to rev really
high trying to keep the set speed
where's the little peep yours listen to
little peep the whole way here but now
I'm on periscope so I don't think my
father can Spotify in periscope at the
same time
doesn't have a left lane here okay
that's not great there we go
no torque flash no torque flash
definitely not no Tesla's yeah kind of
open a tassel support little piece
popular everywhere man oh you mean
Mercedes class A's your late cut in oh
look at that MPC breaking I know it's so
sad
even headlines like you know you'll love
me when I die and there's like it's so
true yeah clear sense there's no no yeah
put your own radar on it it's not that
hard this turn is crazy
get over to this Lane and see this new
model miss detects the other side of the
bike lane at the lane yeah just like
splits
fireable as well
we need a better solution to this
yeah we're running with the new model um
so the new model is not out on the
development branch yet we're still
testing the new model it just got
finished training last night we had some
issues in the machine learning
Department there's been some personnel
changes so I made this model myself and
it's kind of well it's coming along can
we make a left turn across traffic now
no why would you want to do that
unprotected laughs sir a huge problem
I'm doing protected laughs kids
now projected love so I should you
choice of accidents
now I'm going to run this route through
the ground truthing pipeline
no you're saying I have a bad connection
there probably I'm gonna run this route
through the ground truthing pipeline
don't go there
[Music]
is pushed out okay this model needs some
this model needs some some some love
exits exits pretty soon aren't that hard
yeah well rav4 is here there's our Prius
there's our trash cans fuck this someone
took my parking spot anyway to get sharp
returns on the Civic now fired any
feature car for 2018
keep cool always keep them cool man uh
we'll be back on Wi-Fi 9-1-1
what about 9-1-1 don't call 9-1-1 Broce
why why would i call 911
Kamri TSP support what's up with this
911 YouTube live like periscope pros you
can reach SSP support that'll be soon
and watching this in the highway don't
usually phone and drive kids no who
cares about parking park your own damn
car other new sensor the sensor is
exciting what is up with you call mine
what it's like some wine and a brand new
song I think home no no parking no
talking on a car okay alright how do you
ban people on periscope next person says
neither one gets banned
it's called alarmism you guys it's the
media does the media's evil what park
only like a woman that sounds sexist
don't be sexist any news with old car
support I don't know man go on the old
car channel and slack oh no no no you
can park your own car
alright alright between 9 9 9 1 and an
auto fogging know the old car you gotta
ask the people on the slack my favorite
car oh man I said Mercedes s-class I
like that car all right this guy's band
block yeah oh man I love batting peoples
and stuff I said number one and I won't
want insta ban that's one nine nine nine
that's a little bit close to 9 1 1 now
I'll ban you good alright this is just
turned into a stupid rant yeah so enjoy
open pilot zero point three point nine
and hoodies you bought a hoodie if
you're if you bought a hoodie yeah
they'll ship very soon yeah bye how do
you say shit pretty soon cheers guys
0.09
I'll go get it rap for you
yeah fat rat for all right no I see oh
no all right all right all right all
right you guys lit